bitdoze.com 2013-09-11

# Bit Doze Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you place an order.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

; To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

; To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

 **Do we use cookies?**

www.bitdoze.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.bitdoze.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.bitdoze.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our [advertising](http://www.bitdoze.com/advertising/advertising/ "advertising") partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….  
Google Adsense  
Clickbank

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.bitdoze.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

www.bitdoze.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or [services](http://www.bitdoze.com/services/ "services") on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may [contact](http://www.bitdoze.com/contact/ "contact") us using the information below.

http://www.bitdoze.com

bitdoze1[@]gmail[.]com
